Z. JONNY KONG

+1(310) 498-9627 \$\diamondraphi\text{kong102@purdue.edu} \diamondraphi\text{www.jonnykong.com}

I am experienced in and enjoys building **networked systems, mobile systems, and systems for machine learning**. Recent focus is on building Machine-Learning-as-a-Service (MLaaS) serving systems for GPU clusters to serve a large amounts of concurrent requests with SLA guarantees.

EDUCATION

Purdue UniversityWest Lafayette, IN, U.S.Ph.D. in Electrical and Computer EngineeringAug 2020 - PresentUniversity of California, Los AngelesLos Angeles, CA, U.S.M.S. in Computer ScienceSep 2018 - June 2020Beihang UniversityBeijing, ChinaB.E. in AutomationSep 2014 - June 2018

RESEARCH AND PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Purdue UniversityWest Lafayette, IN, U.S.Research AssistantAug 2020 - Present

Advisor: Prof. Y. Charlie Hu

- Designed a machine-learning-as-a-service (MLaaS) framework for heterogeneous GPU clusters that exploits model parallelism to improve server capacities, improving serving throughput by 16.7%-52.8% [1]
- Designed an MLaaS framework for serving edge-assisted AR mobile apps, that maximizes the capacities of GPU servers and serves 1.7-6.9x more clients [2]
- Designed MLaaS frameworks that optimize the overall accuracy of an AR mobile app that offloads multiple tasks to an edge GPU server, improving the overall accuracy by 7.6%-14.3% [4]
- Performed measurement studies on next-generation wireless networks, e.g. 5G [3] [9] and 802.11ad [7]
- Designed edge-assisted AR mobile applications [10] [11], and conducted measurement studies on their performance over 5G networks [5] [6]

University of California, Los Angeles

Research Assistant Advisor: Prof. Lixia Zhang Los Angeles, CA, U.S. Oct 2018 - Jun 2020

- Designed data synchronization protocols [8] [13], a transport-layer protocol for Named Data Networking (NDN)

PUBLICATIONS

Conference Papers

- [1] **Z. Jonny Kong***, Qiang Xu*, Y. Charlie Hu. "IPIPE: Enabling Effective DNN Serving on Heterogeneous GPU Clusters via Model Parallelism". Under submission. (* co-primary)
- [2] **Z. Jonny Kong***, Qiang Xu*, Y. Charlie Hu. "ARISE: An Accuracy-Aware Proactive Framework for Serving Concurrent Edge-Assisted AR Clients". Under submission. (* co-primary)
- [3] Moinak Ghoshal*, Imran Khan*, **Z. Jonny Kong***, Phuc Dinh, Jiayi Meng, Y. Charlie Hu, Dimitrios Koutsonikolas. "Performance of Cellular Networks on the Wheels". In **ACM IMC 2023**. (* co-primary)
- [4] **Z. Jonny Kong***, Qiang Xu*, Jiayi Meng, Y. Charlie Hu. "AccuMO: Accuracy-Centric Multitask Offloading in Edge-Assisted Mobile Augmented Reality". In **ACM MobiCom 2023**. (*co-primary)

Last Updated: Dec 2023 Page 1 of 2

- [5] Moinak Ghoshal*, **Z. Jonny Kong***, Qiang Xu*, Zixiao Lu, Shivang Aggarwal, Imran Khan, Jiayi Meng, Yuanjie Li, Y. Charlie Hu, Dimitrios Koutsonikolas. "Can 5G mmWave Enable Edge-Assisted Real-Time Object Detection for Augmented Reality?". In **IEEE MASCOTS 2023**. (*co-primary)
- [6] Moinak Ghoshal, Pranab Dash, **Zhaoning Kong**, Qiang Xu, Y. Charlie Hu, Dimitrios Koutsonikolas, Yuanjie Li. "Can 5G mmWave Support Multi-User AR Apps?". In **PAM 2022**. [pdf]
- [7] Shivang Aggarwal, **Zhaoning Kong**, Moinak Ghoshal, Y. Charlie Hu, Dimitrios Koutsonikolas. "Throughput Prediction on 60 GHz Mobile Devices for High-Bandwidth, Latency-Sensitive Applications". In **PAM 2021 (Best Dataset Award)**. [pdf]
- [8] Tianxiang Li, **Zhaoning Kong**, Spyridon Mastorakis, Lixia Zhang. "Distributed Dataset Synchronization in Disruptive Networks". In **IEEE MASS 2019**. [pdf]

Workshops & Posters

- [9] Moinak Ghoshal*, **Z. Jonny Kong***, Qiang Xu*, Zixiao Lu, Shivang Aggarwal, Imran Khan, Yuanjie Li, Y. Charlie Hu, and Dimitrios Koutsonikolas. "An In-Depth Study of Uplink Performance of 5G mmWave Networks". In **ACM SIGCOMM 5G-MeMU Workshop '22**. (* co-primary) [pdf]
- [10] Jiayi Meng, **Z. Jonny Kong**, Y. Charlie Hu, Mun Gi Choi, Dhananjay Lal. "Do We Need Sophisticated System Design for Edge-assisted Augmented Reality?". In **ACM EdgeSys 2022 (Best Paper Award)**. [pdf]
- [11] Jiayi Meng*, **Zhaoning Kong***, Qiang Xu, Y. Charlie Hu. "Do Larger (More Accurate) Deep Neural Network Models Help in Edge-assisted Augmented Reality?". In **ACM SIGCOMM NAI Workshop '21**. (*co-primary) [pdf]
- [12] Lana Ramjit, **Zhaoning Kong**, Ravi Netravali, Eugene Wu. "Physical Visualization Design (demo)". In **ACM SIGMOD 2020**. [pdf]
- [13] Tianxiang Li, **Zhaoning Kong**, Lixia Zhang. "Supporting Delay Tolerant Networking: A Comparative Study of Epidemic Routing and NDN". In **IEEE ICC '20 ICN-SRA workshop**. [pdf]

SELECTED AWARDS

Research Awards

- Best Paper Award, EdgeSys '22
- Best Dataset Award, PAM '21

Student Awards

- National Scholarship of China, 2017 (Top 0.2% nationwide)

PROFESSIONAL SERVICES

Journal Reviewers: IEEE Network, Computer Communications **Artifact Evaluation Committee (AEC)**: ACM MobiSys 2023, SOSP 2023

TEACHING ASSISTANT

ECE 26400 Advanced C Programming, Fall '20, Spring '21, Summer '21, Purdue University CS 151B Computer Systems Architecture, Winter '20, UCLA CS 217A Internet Architecture and Protocols, Fall '19, UCLA

Last Updated: Dec 2023 Page 2 of 2